|| LAB-NAME: Demo Lab

|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	a. Bunsen Burner
	Apply heat using the Bunsen Burner until T ≈ 320 K."
	Requirements: [(Temperature:320:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	a. Bunsen Burner
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	a. Bunsen Burner
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	a. Cooling Coil
	Apply the cooling coil until T ≈ 300 K."
	Requirements: [(Temperature:300:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	b. Cooling Coil
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	b. Cooling Coil
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	c. Weight
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"(c)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	c. Weight
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	d. Balloon
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"(c)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property (P,V,T) is being held constant and which one(s) are changing and in what way.
	d. Balloon
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [word-bank]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"e. Stops
Apply a stop in the two-phase or vapor region. Apply heat until the simulation volume reaches the volume of the stop.
As you continue to apply heat, which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume"(c), "Temperature", "Entropy", "Enthalpy"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if T = 373.15 K and P < P_sat?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-Phase"(c), "Superheated Vapor"]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if T = 373.15 K and P > P_sat?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid"(c), "Two-Phase", "Superheated Vapor"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if P = 101 kPa and T > 373.15 K?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-Phase", "Superheated Vapor"(c)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if P = 101 kPa and T < 373.15 K?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid"(c), "Two-Phase", "Superheated Vapor"]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| END



